{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/5187","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5187","name":"Fulin","address":"8677 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48206","owner":"Wei Zhong Lin","licenseNumber":"083447","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.09812,42.37202","geojson":{"id":"5187","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.098118126,42.372018387]},"properties":{"name":"Fulin","owner":"Wei Zhong Lin","address":"8677 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48206","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"083447","establishmentid":"5187","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"2282","name":"China One","address":"8677 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"4109","name":"Fulin Restaurant","address":"8677  Rosa Parks Ave.","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"3006","name":"Robinson Dairy Vending","address":"2021 Blaine","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"4567","name":"Koolies","address":"2021 Blaine","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"1344","name":"Williams Recreation Center","address":"8431 Rosa Parks","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"942","name":"Crosman Alternative High School","address":"8820 Woodrow Wilson","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"865","name":"Thirkell Elementary","address":"7724 Fourteenth","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"51622971","name":"The Congregation Detroit, LLC.","address":"9321 Rosa Parks Blvd.","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"677","name":"Bull Dog Enterprises","address":"1467 Clairmont","zipcode":"48206"},{"establishmentid":"1435","name":"A & A Dairy Cream","address":"8359 Linwood","zipcode":"48206"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61535","inspectionDate":"2022-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not properly","subProblem":"Worn","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"1-101.10","violationDescription":"These provisions shall be known as the Food Code, hereinafter referred to as \"this Code.\"   ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"60008","inspectionDate":"2022-03-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"56537","inspectionDate":"2021-10-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"55013","inspectionDate":"2021-05-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not properly","subProblem":"Worn","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53258","inspectionDate":"2020-10-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"50272","inspectionDate":"2020-01-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"48685","inspectionDate":"2019-08-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45037","inspectionDate":"2019-02-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"43191","inspectionDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"40498","inspectionDate":"2017-10-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Utensil(s) knives","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"by the rear Prep sink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2010-01-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."}]},{"inspectionid":"38419","inspectionDate":"2017-03-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal product(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from each other","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep separate."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36448","inspectionDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"COUNTER","subLocation":"At the Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not marked with a consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Cooler (undercounter)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\n         (2)     The container; and\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Eating","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Eat only in designated areas as restricted above."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Do not prop door open."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5187"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}